<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog</title>
  
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://yoursite.com/"/>
  <updated>2018-06-16T07:53:10.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://yoursite.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Kangshu</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Regression&#39;</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2018/06/16/Regression/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2018/06/16/Regression/</id>
    <published>2018-06-16T07:53:09.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-06-16T07:53:10.000Z</updated>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>【Tool】 Git Basic in Practice (II)</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2018/06/03/git/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2018/06/03/git/</id>
    <published>2018-06-03T12:03:53.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-06-06T07:03:52.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Working-with-remotes"><a href="#Working-with-remotes" class="headerlink" title="Working with remotes"></a>Working with remotes</h2><p>Note: Remote repositories can be on your local machine.It is entirely possible that you can be working with a “remote” repository that is, in fact, on the same host you are. The word “remote” does not necessarily imply that the repository is somewhere else on the network or Internet, only that it is elsewhere. Working with such a remote repository would still involve all the standard pushing, pulling and fetching operations as with any other remote.</p><h3 id="Showing-Your-Remotes"><a href="#Showing-Your-Remotes" class="headerlink" title="Showing Your Remotes"></a>Showing Your Remotes</h3><p>To see which remote servers you have configured, you can run:</p><pre><code class="bash">$ git remote</code></pre><p>You can also specify <code>-v</code>, which shows you the URLs that Git has stored for the shortname to be used when reading and writing to that remote.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;h2 id=&quot;Working-with-remotes&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Working-with-remotes&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Working with remotes&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Working with remotes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Git" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/Git/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How to Write a Research Proposal</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2018/05/30/How-to-Write-a-Research-Proposal/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2018/05/30/How-to-Write-a-Research-Proposal/</id>
    <published>2018-05-30T14:19:59.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-05-30T14:28:50.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Most students and beginning researchers do not fully understand what a research proposal means, nor do they understand its importance. To put it bluntly, one’s research is only as a good as one’s proposal. An ill-conceived proposal dooms the project even if it somehow gets through the Thesis Supervisory Committee. A high quality proposal, on the other hand, not only promises success for the project, but also impresses your Thesis Committee about your potential as a researcher.</p><p>A <strong>research proposal </strong>is intended to convince others that you have a worthwhile research project and that you have the competence and the work-plan to complete it. Generally, a research proposal should contain all the key elements involved in the research process and include sufficient information for the readers to evaluate the proposed study.</p><p>Regardless of your research area and the methodology you choose, all research proposals must address the following questions: What you plan to accomplish, why you want to do it and how you are going to do it.</p><p>The proposal should have sufficient information to convince your readers that you have an important research idea, that you have a good grasp of the relevant literature and the major issues, and that your methodology is sound.</p><p>The quality of your research proposal depends not only on the quality of your proposed project, but also on the quality of your proposal writing. A good research project may run the risk of rejection simply because the proposal is poorly written. Therefore, it pays if your writing is coherent, clear and compelling.</p><p>This paper focuses on proposal writing rather than on the development of research ideas.</p><h2 id="Title"><a href="#Title" class="headerlink" title="Title:"></a>Title:</h2><p>It should be concise and descriptive. For example, the phrase, “An investigation of . . .” could be omitted. Often titles are stated in terms of a functional relationship, because such titles clearly indicate the independent and dependent variables. However, if possible, think of an informative but catchy title. An effective title not only pricks the reader’s interest, but also predisposes him/her favourably towards the proposal.</p><h2 id="Abstract"><a href="#Abstract" class="headerlink" title="Abstract"></a>Abstract</h2><p>It is a brief summary of approximately 300 words. It should include the research question, the rationale for the study, the hypothesis (if any), the method and the main findings. Descriptions of the method may include the design, procedures, the sample and any instruments that will be used.</p><h2 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction"></a>Introduction</h2><p>The main purpose of the introduction is to provide the necessary background or context for your research problem. How to frame the research problem is perhaps the biggest problem in proposal writing.</p><p>If the research problem is framed in the context of a general, rambling literature review, then the research question may appear trivial and uninteresting. However, if the same question is placed in the context of a very focused and current research area, its significance will become evident.</p><p>Unfortunately, there are no hard and fast rules on how to frame your research question just as there is no prescription on how to write an interesting and informative opening paragraph. A lot depends on your creativity, your ability to think clearly and the depth of your understanding of problem areas.</p><p>However, try to place your research question in the context of either a current “hot” area, or an older area that remains viable. Secondly, you need to provide a brief but appropriate historical backdrop. Thirdly, provide the contemporary context in which your proposed research question occupies the central stage. Finally, identify “key players” and refer to the most relevant and representative publications. In short, try to paint your research question in broad brushes and at the same time bring out its significance.</p><p>The introduction typically begins with a general statement of the problem area, with a focus on a specific research problem, to be followed by the rational or justification for the proposed study. The introduction generally covers the following elements: </p><ul><li>State the research problem, which is often referred to as the purpose of the study.</li><li>Provide the context and set the stage for your research question in such a way as to show its necessity and importance.</li><li>Present the rationale of your proposed study and clearly indicate why it is worth doing.</li><li>Briefly describe the major issues and sub-problems to be addressed by your research.</li><li>Identify the key independent and dependent variables of your experiment. Alternatively, specify the phenomenon you want to study.</li><li>State your hypothesis or theory, if any. For exploratory or phenomenological research, you may not have any hypotheses. (Please do not confuse the hypothesis with the statistical null hypothesis.)</li><li>Set the delimitation or boundaries of your proposed research in order to provide a clear focus.</li><li>Provide definitions of key concepts. (This is optional.)</li></ul><h2 id="Literature-Review"><a href="#Literature-Review" class="headerlink" title="Literature Review"></a>Literature Review</h2><p>Sometimes the literature review is incorporated into the introduction section. However, most professors prefer a separate section, which allows a more thorough review of the literature.</p><p>The literature review serves several important functions:</p><ul><li>Ensures that you are not “reinventing the wheel”.</li><li>Gives credits to those who have laid the groundwork for your research.</li><li>Demonstrates your knowledge of the research problem.</li><li>Demonstrates your understanding of the theoretical and research issues related to your research question.</li><li>Shows your ability to critically evaluate relevant literature information.</li><li>Indicates your ability to integrate and synthesize the existing literature.</li><li>Provides new theoretical insights or develops a new model as the conceptual framework for your research.</li><li>Convinces your reader that your proposed research will make a significant and substantial contribution to the literature (i.e., resolving an important theoretical issue or filling a major gap in the literature).</li></ul><p>Most students’ literature reviews suffer from the following problems:</p><ul><li>Lacking organization and structure<ul><li>Lacking focus, unity and coherence</li><li>Being repetitive and verbose</li><li>Failing to cite influential papers</li><li>Failing to keep up with recent developments</li><li>Failing to critically evaluate cited papers</li><li>Citing irrelevant or trivial references</li><li>Depending too much on secondary sources</li></ul></li></ul><p>Your scholarship and research competence will be questioned if any of the above applies to your proposal.</p><p>There are different ways to organize your literature review. Make use of subheadings to bring order and coherence to your review. For example, having established the importance of your research area and its current state of development, you may devote several subsections on related issues as: theoretical models, measuring instruments, cross-cultural and gender differences, etc.</p><p>It is also helpful to keep in mind that you are telling a story to an audience. Try to tell it in a stimulating and engaging manner. Do not bore them, because it may lead to rejection of your worthy proposal. (Remember: Professors and scientists are human beings too.)</p><h2 id="Methods"><a href="#Methods" class="headerlink" title="Methods"></a>Methods</h2><p>The Method section is very important because it tells your Research Committee how you plan to tackle your research problem. It will provide your work plan and describe the activities necessary for the completion of your project.</p><p>The guiding principle for writing the Method section is that it should contain sufficient information for the reader to determine whether methodology is sound. Some even argue that a good proposal should contain sufficient details for another qualified researcher to implement the study.</p><p>You need to demonstrate your knowledge of alternative methods and make the case that your approach is the most appropriate and most valid way to address your research question.</p><p>Please note that your research question may be best answered by qualitative research. However, since most mainstream psychologists are still biased against qualitative research, especially the phenomenological variety, you may need to justify your qualitative method.</p><p>Furthermore, since there are no well-established and widely accepted canons in qualitative analysis, your method section needs to be more elaborate than what is required for traditional quantitative research. More importantly, the data collection process in qualitative research has a far greater impact on the results as compared to quantitative research. That is another reason for greater care in describing how you will collect and analyze your data. (How to write the Method section for qualitative research is a topic for another paper.)</p><p>For quantitative studies, the method section typically consists of the following sections:</p><ul><li>Design -Is it a questionnaire study or a laboratory experiment? What kind of design do you choose?</li><li>Subjects or participants Who will take part in your study ? What kind of sampling procedure do you use?</li><li>Instruments What kind of measuring instruments or questionnaires do you use? Why do you choose them? Are they valid and reliable?</li><li>Procedure How do you plan to carry out your study? What activities are involved? How long does it take?</li></ul><h2 id="Results"><a href="#Results" class="headerlink" title="Results"></a>Results</h2><p>Obviously you do not have results at the proposal stage. However, you need to have some idea about what kind of data you will be collecting, and what statistical procedures will be used in order to answer your research question or test you hypothesis.</p><h2 id="Discussion"><a href="#Discussion" class="headerlink" title="Discussion"></a>Discussion</h2><p>It is important to convince your reader of the potential impact of your proposed research. You need to communicate a sense of enthusiasm and confidence without exaggerating the merits of your proposal. That is why you also need to mention the limitations and weaknesses of the proposed research, which may be justified by time and financial constraints as well as by the early developmental stage of your research area.</p><p>Common Mistakes in Proposal Writing</p><ul><li>Failure to provide the proper context to frame the research question.</li><li>Failure to delimit the boundary conditions for your research.</li><li>Failure to cite landmark studies.</li><li>Failure to accurately present the theoretical and empirical contributions by other researchers.</li><li>Failure to stay focused on the research question.</li><li>Failure to develop a coherent and persuasive argument for the proposed research.</li><li>Too much detail on minor issues, but not enough detail on major issues.</li><li>Too much rambling -going “all over the map” without a clear sense of direction. (The best proposals move forward with ease and grace like a seamless river.)</li><li>Too many citation lapses and incorrect references.</li><li>Too long or too short.</li><li>Failing to follow the APA style.</li><li>Slopping writing.</li></ul>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;Most students and beginning researchers do not fully understand what a research proposal means, nor do they understand its importance. To
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Acdemic" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/Acdemic/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>【Tool】 Git Basic in Practice (I)</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2018/05/22/operation/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2018/05/22/operation/</id>
    <published>2018-05-22T07:43:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-06-03T12:06:22.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Git</strong> is a distributed <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Version_control_system" title="Version control system" target="_blank" rel="noopener">version control system</a> for tracking changes in computer files and coordinating work on those files among multiple people.<br>Git has three main states that your files can reside in: committed, modified, and staged:</p><ul><li>Committed means that the data is safely stored in your local database.</li><li>Modified means that you have changed the file but have not committed it to your database yet.</li><li>Staged means that you have marked a modified file in its current version to go into your next commit snapshot.<br><img src="https://git-scm.com/book/en/v2/images/areas.png" alt=""><br>Figure 1. Working tree, staging area, and Git directory.<h2 id="Installing-Git"><a href="#Installing-Git" class="headerlink" title="Installing Git"></a>Installing Git</h2><ul><li><strong>Installing on Windows</strong><br>The most official build is available for download on the Git website. Just go to <a href="http://git-scm.com/download/win" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://git-scm.com/download/win</a> and the download will start automatically.</li><li><strong>Installing on Linux (Ubuntu/Debain)</strong><br>If you’re on a Debian-based distribution, such as Ubuntu, try <code>apt</code>:<figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ apt-get install git</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></li></ul></li></ul><h2 id="Git-configure-tooling"><a href="#Git-configure-tooling" class="headerlink" title="Git configure tooling"></a>Git configure tooling</h2><p>Git comes with a tool called git config that lets you get and set configuration variables that control all aspects of how Git looks and operates. These variables can be stored in three different places:</p><ol><li><code>/etc/gitconfig</code> file: Contains values applied to every user on the system and all their repositories. If you pass the option <code>--system</code> to git config, it reads and writes from this file specifically. (Because this is a system configuration file, you would need administrative or superuser privilege to make changes to it.)</li><li><code>~/.gitconfig</code>or <code>~/.config/git/config</code> file: Values specific personally to you, the user. You can make Git read and write to this file specifically by passing the –global option.</li><li>config file in the Git directory (that is, <code>.git/config</code>) of whatever repository you’re currently using: Specific to that single repository.<br>The first thing you should do when you install Git is to set your user name and email address. This is important because every Git commit uses this information, and it’s immutably baked into the commits you start creating:<figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ git config --global user.name <span class="string">"John Doe"</span></span><br><span class="line">$ git config --global user.email johndoe@example.com</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></li></ol><p>If you want to override this with a different name or email address for specific projects, you can run the command without the <code>--global</code> option when you’re in that project.</p><h2 id="Git-commands"><a href="#Git-commands" class="headerlink" title="Git commands"></a>Git commands</h2><h3 id="Creating-or-cloning-a-Git-repository"><a href="#Creating-or-cloning-a-Git-repository" class="headerlink" title="Creating or cloning a Git repository"></a>Creating or cloning a Git repository</h3><p>If you have a project directory that is currently not under version control and you want to start controlling it with Git, you first need to go to that project’s directory and type:<br><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ git init</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>This creates a new subdirectory named <code>.git</code> that contains all of your necessary repository files — a Git repository skeleton. At this point, nothing in your project is tracked yet. If you want to start version-controlling existing files (as opposed to an empty directory), you should probably begin tracking those files and do an initial commit. You can accomplish that with a few <code>git add</code> commands.<br>If you want to get a copy of an existing Git repository — for example, a project you’d like to contribute to — the command you need is <code>git clone</code> like this:<br><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ git <span class="built_in">clone</span> https://github.com/libgit2/libgit2</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><h3 id="Make-Changes"><a href="#Make-Changes" class="headerlink" title="Make Changes"></a>Make Changes</h3><p>If you have made changes in your profiles,you can list all new or modified files by typing:<br><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ git status</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>While the git status output is pretty comprehensive, it’s also quite wordy. Git also has a short status flag so you can see your changes in a more compact way. If you run <code>git status -s</code> or <code>git status --short</code><br>In order to begin tracking a new file, you use the command:<br><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ git add</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>To see what you’ve changed but not yet staged, type:<br><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ git diff</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>That command compares what is in your working directory with what is in your staging area. The result tells you the changes you’ve made that you haven’t yet staged.</p><p>If you want to see what you’ve staged that will go into your next commit, you can use <code>git diff --staged</code>. This command compares your staged changes to your last commit.And  you can use <code>git diff --cached</code>to see what you’ve staged so far.</p><h3 id="Group-Changes"><a href="#Group-Changes" class="headerlink" title="Group Changes"></a>Group Changes</h3><p>To List out all local branches in the current repository, you can run:<br><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ git branch</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>If you want to create a new branch, you can use command <code>git branch [branch-name]</code>(command <code>git branch -d [branch-name]</code> for deleting), then use the command <code>git checkout [branch-name]</code>to switch to the specified branch and update the working directory.<br>Certainly,To create a new branch and switch to it at the same time, you can run:<br><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ git checkout -b [branch-name]</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><h3 id="Review-History"><a href="#Review-History" class="headerlink" title="Review History"></a>Review History</h3><p>To view the commit history of the current branch, you should use the command:<br><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ git <span class="built_in">log</span></span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>Certainly, common options to <code>$ git log</code> helps you to output more freely like sql server. Options are listed in Table.1</p><table border="1"><br>  <tr><br>    <th>Option</th><br>    <th>Description</th><br>  </tr><br>  <tr><br>    <td>–pretty=oneline</td><br>    <td>Print each commit on a single line</td><br>  </tr><br> <tr><br>    <td>–pretty=format:</td><br>    <td> Outputyour own log output format</td><br>  </tr><br><tr><br>    <td>–patch</td><br>    <td>Show the patch introduced with each commit.</td><br>  </tr><br><tr><br>    <td>–stat</td><br>    <td>Show statistics for files modified in each commit.</td><br>  </tr><br></table>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Git&lt;/strong&gt; is a distributed &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Version_control_system&quot; title=&quot;Version control system&quot; targe
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Git" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/Git/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello World</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2018/05/13/hello-world/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2018/05/13/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2018-05-13T06:30:08.180Z</published>
    <updated>2017-10-28T00:39:58.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to <a href="https://hexo.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hexo</a>! This is your very first post. Check <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">documentation</a> for more info. If you get any problems when using Hexo, you can find the answer in <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/troubleshooting.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">troubleshooting</a> or you can ask me on <a href="https://github.com/hexojs/hexo/issues" target="_blank" rel="noopener">GitHub</a>.</p><h2 id="Quick-Start"><a href="#Quick-Start" class="headerlink" title="Quick Start"></a>Quick Start</h2><h3 id="Create-a-new-post"><a href="#Create-a-new-post" class="headerlink" title="Create a new post"></a>Create a new post</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo new <span class="string">"My New Post"</span></span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/writing.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Writing</a></p><h3 id="Run-server"><a href="#Run-server" class="headerlink" title="Run server"></a>Run server</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo server</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/server.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Server</a></p><h3 id="Generate-static-files"><a href="#Generate-static-files" class="headerlink" title="Generate static files"></a>Generate static files</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo generate</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/generating.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Generating</a></p><h3 id="Deploy-to-remote-sites"><a href="#Deploy-to-remote-sites" class="headerlink" title="Deploy to remote sites"></a>Deploy to remote sites</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo deploy</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/deployment.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Deployment</a></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;a href=&quot;https://hexo.io/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Hexo&lt;/a&gt;! This is your very first post. Check &lt;a href=&quot;https://hexo.
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
